Top Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- SQL (Databases)
- GitHub
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Microsoft Visual Studio Code
- Figma
- Communication
- Creative
- Team Player
- Work Under Pressure

Additional Computer Skills

- PHP
- React
- Node
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Microsoft Excel
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe Dreamweaver
- Adobe Animate
- Adobe InDesign
- Unity

Additional Creative Skills

- 2D Art
- Photography
- Typography
- Creative Writing
- Story Boarding
- Photo Editing
- Video Editing

Certificates

2024 Google Analytics Individual Qualification

2020 - 2021 Microsoft Creative Suite

2019 - 2020 Adobe Certified Associate Creative Cloud

Michael Alfonso

<u>aalfonso94848@gmail.com</u> | (407) 715-0845 | www.linkedin.com/in/michaelanthony-alfonso

Summary

Highly motivated and hard-working Web Designer with 2 years of experience in creating user-friendly websites, mobile applications, and UX designs. Experienced in user-testing, GitHub collaborations, user flow, navigation structures, high-fi wireframing, reactive design, and optimizing website performance. Always looking for new ways to improve and expand my skills.

Work Experience

App Designer/Developer

Nov 2022 - March 2023

- Designed hi-fi wire frames for various recording and note taking mobile applications using Adobe XD and Figma software's (including functionality such as checklists, record management, and account settings).
- Conducted user testing to improve design elements, experience, and seamlessness.
- Developed basic e-commerce and recording applications with React, allowing functionality such as adding items to be sold, adding total values in a shoppingcart, and uploading images/records to be stored.
- Utilized various resource libraries for the implementation of icons.

AR XD Designer

Sept 2021 - May 2022

- Designed functional, hi-fi Adobe XD prototypes which include menu's, UI, and navigational elements.
- Produced logo's, icons, backgrounds, and button designs via Photoshop.
- Performed various user-testing protocols to document bugs/issues for effective redesign and simplification of UI and navigation.

Personal Project – Restaurant Website

Sept 2020 – April 2021

- Produced a fully designed restaurant website for a fictional location complete with social media tags, form elements, CSS styling, and more.
- Utilized creative commons imagery and self-produced icons/images for the throughout the various pages.
- Created fully functional navigational elements, appropriate linking to resources, and an online ordering system.

Education

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Digital Media University of Central Florida - (August 2021 - December 2023)

Associate Degree, Graphic Design Seminole State College of Florida · (August 2019 - May 2021)